Ivan Chornyi

Senior DevOps/SRE

Email: cv@chornyi.rocks

Linkedin: ichornyi

About Me

I am a Senior DevOps Engineer with huge developer experience in past(~6 years). During my career I worked with various programming languages such as PHP, JS and Python but always had a passion to infrastructure and whole picture understanding how applications should work so I passed GCP associate certification, mastered k8s and switched to the DevOps position. I believe my experience helps me to better cooperate with developers and create suitable infrastructure and automate routine tasks which will give the best possible result for the project.

Skills

Programming languages: Bash, PHP, Python, Javascript, Typescript, Go

Additional technologies: OOP, HTML, CSS, YAML

Frameworks/CMS: Symfony/Laravel/Phalcon, Codeception, Magento 1.x CE/EE, Wordpress,

Django, Flask, Angular X, NodeJS, Gin, Bootstrap, Selenium

Tools: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Helm, Vagrant, Ansible, Terraform, Vault, Spinnaker, CircleCl,

Gitlab

Support Tools: Jira, Confluence, Pagerduty, HP LoadRunner

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Memcache, PostgreSQL, BigQuery

Operating Systems: Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, Raspbian, OS X

Clouds: GCP, AWS

Foreign languages: English(intermediate)

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks

Certifications







Experience

Techstack

Senior DevOps Engineer

April 2024 - Nowadays tech-stack.com

Techstack is a dynamic software development company that specializes in creating and enhancing innovative digital products. Founded in 2014, the company has grown into a team of 170+ professionals, collaborating to deliver high-quality software solutions. Techstack is a trusted technology partner for global clients, including Corel Corporation, and excels in combining expertise, cutting-edge technology, and a collaborative culture to drive product success.

In the CloudOps team, I worked on diverse automation and infrastructure management tasks, supported subdepartments, and improved existing infrastructure code for better performance and scalability. Tech stack:

- GCP
- Go
- Python
- Terraform
- GKE(k8s)
- CircleCI

SoftServe provides services in the fields of big data, Internet of things, cloud computing, DevOps, e-commerce, computer security,

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 2/6

SoftServe

Senior DevOps Engineer

April 2021 - April 2024 www.softserveinc.com

MWDN

SRE

August 2020 - April 2021 mwdn.com experience design, and health care. With its United States headquarters in Austin, Texas and European headquarters in Lviv, Ukraine, the company employed more than 10,000 people in offices in 2021.

As a member of CloudOps team I participated in various number of activities such as: strategic infrastructure/automation development, support of incoming requests from developers, support of Data department, various infrastructure improvements and automation. Tech stack:

- GCP
- AWS
- Terraform
- k8s
- CircleCI/Spinnaker

MWDN is an international development company with headquarters in Israel and development center in Kharkiv, Ukraine.
Founded in 2002 by highly skilled project managers, MWDN has developed a significant number of successful projects concerning complex medical systems and cardiac monitoring in the past decade and a half.
MWDN is also very proud of cooperation with some of the most successful international startups and a great experience in medical, web and mobile software development.

Participated as a member of the Cloud SRE team. The team is responsible for maintaining the medical imaging systems infrastructure and administering the GCP. My main responsibilites:

- compliance monitoring system development and maintenance for GCP infrastructure
- development of application for synthetic monitoring of webapplications
- cost-savings automation for GCP

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 3/6

infrastructure monitoring automation

GlobalLogic is a Digital Product Engineering
Services company that was founded in 2000
and is headquartered in San Jose, California. It
is a privately held company funded by Partners
Group and CPP Investment Board. GlobalLogic
provides software product development
services, including experience design, complex
systems engineering, content engineering, and
self-contained engineering labs.

Development, maintenance and optimization of CRM for Forex brokers and various support and internal tools. Servers setup and optimization. Bugfix. CRM modules development from scratch. Ontechnical call support experience. Experience in upgrade PHP 5.5->7.1->7.4. The CRM core has been totally rewritten due to optimization purposes. Migration from AWS to GCP. Development of internal tools using Django/Flask.

Regular business trips. Half a year of experience in the role of Team Lead. Direct communication with customer.

Ronis is a leading eCommerce development agency that specialises in high converting Magento sites. Founded in 2003, our experienced team build stand-out, successful retail platforms for brands and small businesses.

E-commerce development:

- Development of new Magento(1.x CE and EE) websites
- E-store development and support/maintenance
- API integration (email marketing, analytics and internal custom API's)
- Development of new internal services (like URL shortener, social network, product management tool)

4/6

GlobalLogic

Senior Software Engineer

October 2016 - August 2020 globallogic.com

Ronis Business Tools

PHP Developer

August 2015 - September 2016 roniscommerce.com

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks

- Bug fixing
- Support
- Database optimization
- Internal synchronizations development

Smythisoft

Junior PHP Developer

September 2014 - August 2015 smithysoft.com Fullstack development company. Outsourcing short-term projects.

Development of a wide range of web applications:

- Code implementing and optimization
- Adding new functionality
- Requirements clarification
- Bug fixing
- Support

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 5/6

Education

National University of Radioelectronics

Computer science & Biotechnical medic systems

2006 - 2011

Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics (NURE) is a higher education institution of the highest level of accreditation in Ukraine. It is one of the oldest technology universities in Ukraine, with over 7000 students and 30 scientific centers.

During my time at NURE I learnt most of my key skills that have I have taken through my career such as teamwork and working to tight deadlines. I spent a lot of my free time as a committee member of my faculty taking on *headman* role.

A Little More About Me

- Married
- · Founder of Ukrainian Nissan Rogue Club
- · Starlink volunteer for Armed forces of Ukraine

Alongside my interests in networks and software engineering some of my other interests and hobbies are:

- 3D printing
- · FPV Drone racing
- USA Cars
- · Online shopping
- World digitizing

Ivan Chornyi cv@chornyi.rocks - References on request

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 6/6